<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BuyAtHome</string>
    <string name="server_client_id">AIzaSyBRM59w2KLUvgelFT7g1XwKVq7-ejsUdTE</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">944221395647073</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_laptops">Laptops</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_cart">My Cart</string>
    <string name="action_my_cart">Delete All</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_favourites">MyFavourites</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Register</string>

    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Register now.</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registered! Log Me in.</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search">SearchActivity</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="title_activity_phones">Phones</string>
    <string name="title_activity_phone_accessories">PhoneAccessories</string>
    <string name="title_activity_laptop_accessories">LaptopAccessories</string>
    <string name="title_activity_checkout">Checkout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity2">MainActivity2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_verification">Verification</string>
    <string name="title_activity_most_rated">MostRated</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="title_activity_latest_laptops">LatestLaptops</string>
    <string name="title_activity_latest_phones">LatestPhones</string>
    <string name="title_activity_preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="title_activity_feed">FeedActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_zoom_image">ZoomImage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_name_mail">NameMail</string>
    <string name="action_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">Test</string>

    //time ago
    <string name="time_ago_prefix"></string>
    <string name="time_ago_suffix">ago</string>
    <string name="time_ago_seconds">less than a minute</string>
    <string name="time_ago_minute">about a minute</string>
    <string name="time_ago_minutes">%d minutes</string>
    <string name="time_ago_hour">about an hour</string>
    <string name="time_ago_hours">about %d hours</string>
    <string name="time_ago_day">a day</string>
    <string name="time_ago_days">%d days</string>
    <string name="time_ago_month">about a month</string>
    <string name="time_ago_months">%d months</string>
    <string name="time_ago_year">about a year</string>
    <string name="time_ago_years">%d years</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_new_product">New Product</string>

    <string-array name="get_arrays">
        <!--<item>Voucher</item>
        <item>Other</item>-->
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="url">http://snapt.t15.org/buyathome/</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_phones">Phones</string>
    <string name="title_accessories">Accessories</string>
    <string name="item_deleted">Item deleted</string>
    <string name="item_undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_featured_details">Featured</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="err_msg_landMark">Enter nearest landmark</string>
    <string name="err_msg_city">Enter your current city or town</string>
    <string name="err_msg_phone">Enter your phone number</string>
    <string name="err_msg_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="err_msg_email">Please provide your email</string>
    <string name="action_cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="action_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="action_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delivery_policy">
     <b>1. Delivery Notifications</b>\n
      You will receive an email at the address you have specified when your order has been despatched - this email contains the tracking number/receipt number(if applicable) so you can confirm what is being delivered. You can also choose to have a delivery confirmation sent to your mobile phone via text message.
        \n\n<b>2. Delivery timescales </b>\n
      Next day delivery for items within Nairobi. This is a first in delivery e-commerce in Kenya and applies to any orders confirmed before 2:00pm on business days.For all other regions, BuyAtHome strives to deliver your product within 2-5 business days. BuyAtHome aims to deliver your products within 7 days from the time of order confirmation For all products, our customer service agents will inform you of the expected delivery timeline when confirming your order.
\n\n
     <b>3. Postage method </b>\n
        Optionally, you can choose to have your ordered delivered though POSTA for an additional charge that will include the postage charges. The amounts will be communicated to you when you make your order.
\n\n
     <b>4. Missed deliveries </b>\n
        If you are not in to receive the delivery at the time the delivery is attempted, we will notify you of the missed delivery attempt. This will allow you to either telephone us to arrange a redelivery at a more convenient time.
        If for any reason the item is returned to us (e.g. incorrect address specified, item not called for), then BuyAtHome will inform you immediately by email as soon as we receive the item.  From this point forth, you will be given a choice whether you wish us to redespatch the item or for you to cancel the order.  Please note that for items that were undelivered through fault of the consumer and a refund is requested, BuyAtHome reserve the right to deduct our outwardly shipping fees from the refund total.
\n\n
     <b>5. Late deliveries or despatch</b>\n
        In rare circumstances our shipping capacity can be exceeded and cause a delay of one extra day. BuyAtHome regrets that this situation can occur occasionally, and is an unfortunate situation which is naturally associated with buying online, however this only occurs in rare situations and, should this occur, your order is marked for urgent delivery the following day.
        The other circumstance which may cause a delay is when the delivery service itself has a problem.  This, again, is a rare situation but is unfortunately beyond our control.  In these situations, BuyAtHome will do our very best to take responsibility for the situation and ensure that your order is delivered as quickly as possible.
\n\n
     <b>5.1 Consequential loss for late deliveries</b>\n
        If a delivery is late, e.g. the postal service fails to deliver within the guaranteed timescale, then BuyAtHome will provide a refund of any delivery charges that were charged to you.  If the delivery was free, Watch Shop and Watch Shop Logistics Ltd do not provide financial compensation to cover consequential losses, e.g. Time taken off work to receive deliveries, or the item is intended as a gift, and you purchase the same item from a more expensive retailer.
\n\n
     <b>6. Delivery to business addresses</b>\n
        BuyAtHome allows delivery to alternate delivery addresses including business addresses and places of work. If you do specify a business address for delivery, please ensure that there will be someone available during normal working hours e.g. at reception who can sign for delivery on your behalf.
    </string>

    <!-- BuyAtHome promises to provide you with the best-in-class shopping experience at every step of
     the way. We assure you that all due precautions are taken so that your package are delivered to
     you intact and on time by our delivery partner. Just proceed with your order and we’ll do the
     rest. In case you face any difficulty, you can email us anytime at buyathome2015@gmail.com or
     call us at +254711219490-->
    <string name="server_url">http://nickmuthumbi.com/buyathome/server_scripts/</string>
</resources>
